ILR School Librarian's Office Files /4004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Librarian's Office Files
1948-1990
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Martin P. Catherwood Library
Miller, J. Gormly
Harper, Shirley
/4004
38 cubic feet
38 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Consists mainly of correspondence, reports, and administrative files.
3079814
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 13, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 20, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4139: Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files /4145: ILR School Librarian's Office Additional Files /4156: ILR School Librarian's Office Additional Files /4169: Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files
Harper, Shirley F.; Miller, J. Gormly; Martin P. Catherwood Library.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Library.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
3079814
- State University Librarians' Conference, SUNY April 26, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- State Librarians Conference Utica, N.Y. April 24-26, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Stater Librarians' Conference Plattsburg, New York April 23-24, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- State University Librarians; Conference, SUNY Corning, N.Y. April 1965 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- State University Librarians' Conf. Maritime College, April 20-22, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- State University Librarians Conf. Star Lake, May 11-12, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- State University of New York Librarians' Conference Committee on Personnel Policy, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- State University A-10 Librarians' Conference Committee on Personnel Policy Correspondence, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- State University Librarians' Conference Committee on Personnel Policy Research Materials, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Librarians' Conference Committee on Personnel Policy Draft Reports (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Cornell University Faculty, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Cornell University A1-5 Faculty 1956 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Cornell University A-I.5 Faculty 1958 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Cornell University General AI-11, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Cornell University Graduate School AI-15, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Cornell University AI-20 Intra University Memoranda From ILR Library, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Cornell University Purchasing Department AI-35, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Cornell University Reports A-40, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Cornell University Research A-45, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Cornell University Trustees AI-65 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Cornell University Library - Cornell Library News, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- CUL Staff Ass'n., 1950-1968 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Cornell University Library Inter-Library Memorandum Cornell University Library, 1947-1949 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Cornell University Library Inter-Library Memorandum Cornell University Library, 1952-53, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Cornell University Library Inter-Library Memorandum Cornell University Library, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Cornell University Library Inter-Library Memoranda 1955- (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Cornell University Library Inter-Library Memorandum C.U.L. Staff Memoranda, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Cornell University, Library Interlibrary Memo 1970-75, 1970-1975 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Interlibrary Memos, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- College and Librarian's Meetings - Minutes and Reports, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Library Reorganization, Draft and Proposals, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Cornell University Library, 1955-1957 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Cornell University Library Acquisitions, CUL 1958 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Cornell University Library A-15 Acquisition, CUL 1959 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Cornell University Library Acquisitions, CUL 1960 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- A-15 Cul Acquisitions 1962-69, 1962-1969 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Cornell University Library Acquisitions I.L.R. Standing Order, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Cornell University Library Acquisitions Foreign Periodicals, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- A-15 - ILR Foreign Subscriptions - 1959 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Exchanges for ILR Publications, Acquisitions 1953-59, 1953-1959 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Library Commission pm Univ. Publications, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Cornell University Library Cornell University Library Survey, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Cornell University Library Cornell University Library Survey, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Cornell University Library Cornell University Library Survey, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Directorship of the Libraries 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Serials currently received Commissions, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Serials Currently Received Commissions, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- College of Agriculture Library, 1951-1969 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- BPA Library, 1950-1969 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- College of Engineering, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Human or Home Economics 1950-53, 1950-1953 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Lan Library - 1950-57, 1950-1957 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- College of Veterinary Medicine, 1954-1960 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- CUL Libraries - Librarian's Council, 1950-1953 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- NYSSILR B-1 Community Chest, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- B5 Visitors, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Faculty Committees - Committee on Research and Publications, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- B7 School Conferences, School Meetings, School Advisory Council Meetings, 1946-1963 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- B. NYSSILR B-8 Publicity - Public Relations Office, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- NYSSILR B-10.5 Travel Expense Vouchers, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- NYSSILR B-10.5 Travel Expense Accounts, 1960-1965 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- NYSSILR B-10.5 Travel Expense Accounts, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- B 10.5 Instructions + Travel Schedules, 1950-1969 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- B-10.5 Travel Requests (Box 2, Folder 33)
- B-12 Admin. Conf. 1956-58, 1956-1958 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Administrative Conference 1954-66, 1954-1966 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- B-12 Admin. Conf. 1967 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- B15 Administrative Memoranda 1967-9, 1967-1969 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Administrative Memoranda Faculty Members and Staff, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- B15.1, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Memos to Admin. Aids 1963-69, 1963-1969 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- B.15.B Memos 1968-69, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- B.15.4 Inventory Reports, 1958-1969 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- B-15.1 Faculty Members, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Administrative Memoranda B-15.2 Administrative Assistant, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- NYSSILR B-15.2 Administrative Assistant, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- NYSSILR B-15.2 Memoranda to Administrative Assistant - Staff Changes, 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- B-15.2 Memoranda to Administrative Assistant, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- NYSSILR Administrative Memoranda Dean Catherwood, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- NYSSILR B-15.3 Dean Catherwood, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- NYSSILR B-16 Visiting Lectures (Box 3, Folder 14)
- NYSSILR B-20 Extension Memoranda, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- B-20 Faculty Memoranda - Faculty Legislation, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Faculty Memoranda B-20.5 Adams, L. P., 1976 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Faculty Memoranda Allen, W. H., 1966 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- NYSSILR B-5 Faculty Memoranda Beach, C. K., 1952 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Faculty Memoranda B-20.5 Blumen, Isador, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Brooks, Earl, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Brophy, J. M., 1957 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- B. NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Burling, T., 1952 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- B. NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Dean, Richard, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- B-20 Faculty Memoranda B-20.5 Campbell, James, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Campbell, Ralph, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Faculty Memoranda B-20.5 Campbell, Ralph, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Faculty Memoranda B-20.5 Carpenter, J. T., 1967 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Catherwood, M. P., 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- B-20 Faculty Memoranda B-20.5 Catherwood, M. P., 1960 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Catherwood M. P., 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Catherwood, M. P., 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- NYSSILR B-5 Faculty Memoranda Clark, M. Gardner, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Faculty Memoranda B 20.5 Connors, Wm. E., 1961 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Corvini, R., 1954 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Corvini, Rudolph, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Faculty Memoranda Cullen, Donald, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Faculty Memoranda Cutlip, Scott, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Faculty Memoranda Drotning, John, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Faculty Memoranda Emerson, L. A., 1955 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Estey, Marten, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Ferguson, R. H., 1954 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Foltman, F., 1953 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Faculty Memoranda B-20.5 Friedland, W., 1965 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Faculty Memoranda Freilicher, Frederic, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Culick, Charles A., 1951 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Gordon, Paul, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Faculty Memoranda Hanson, C. Arnold, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- BYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Hanson, C. A., 1954 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Faculty Memoranda Hodges, Wayne, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Faculty Memoranda Irwin, F., 1963 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Jensen, V. H., 1954 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Jehring, J. J., 1951 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Faculty Memoranda Keenahan, Laura, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Konvits, M. R., 1951 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Faculty Committee 1957 - Accreditation Committee (Box 3, Folder 56)
- Faculty Memoranda Konvitz, Milton R., 1954 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Faculty Memoranda Landsberger, Henry A., 1962 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Leighton, A. H. (Box 4, Folder 3)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Val Lorwin, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Faculty Memoranda Dean McConnell, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda McConnell, J. W., 1954 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Faculty Memoranda MacIntyre, Duncan, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda MacIntyre, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda McKelvey, Jean T., 1954 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Faculty Memoranda Martin, Albert A. (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Faculty Memoranda Mesics, Emil, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Faculty Memoranda Mizener, Arthur (Mrs.), 1957 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Faculty Memoranda Dean David D. Moore, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Morton, J. E., 1950 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- NYSSILR B-5 Faculty Memoranda Philomena, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Faculty Memoranda Naas, B. G., 1950 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Neufeld, M. F., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Ornati, Oscar, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Prof. Mark Perlman, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Faculty Memoranda Perrins, Harlan, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Plasha, Frank, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Faculty Memoranda Polisar, Eric, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Ranck, Kathryn, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- NYSSILR Faculty Prof. Robert Raimon, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Faculty Memoranda Raimon, Robert, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Faculty Memoranda Risley, Robert F., 1958 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Sargent, Edward, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Sayles, Leonard R., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Schmidhauser, H. B., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Smith, A. W., 1955 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Strauss, George, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Faculty Memoranda Smith, Alpheus, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Faculty Neil Soslow, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Sturmthal, Adolf, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Prof. Clyde W. Summers, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Tolles, N. A., 1954 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Faculty Memoranda Tolles, N. Arnold, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Whyte, W. F., 1952 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Professor John Windmuller, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- NYSSILR Faculty Memoranda Witte, Edwin E., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Faculty Committees Advisory Panel on International Research, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Faculty Committees Special Committee on Faculty Membership, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Faculty Committees Student-Faculty, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Faculty Committees Scholarships and Awards Comm., 1962 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- NYSSILR B-30 Research + Information Division Reports, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Manual of Administrative Practices and Procedures ILR School, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  Scope and Contents
  Bound
- Library, NYSSILR International Activities: A Program for the Next Ten Years, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- NYSSILR Publications Industrial and Labor Relations, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Publications Abstracts and Annotations -- 1956 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- NYSSILR Publications Abstracts and Annotations, 1950-1953 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- NYSSILR Publications Industrial and Labor Relations Review General, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- NYSSILR Publications Abstracts and Annotations, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- NYSSILR B-40 Student Peersonnel Office Advisory System Graduate Students: Suskind, W. B., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- B. NYSSILR B-40 Student Personnel Advice Memoranda, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- NYSSILR Memoranda to Administrative Asst., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Visiting Professors, Lecturers and other Visitors - 1956 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- B. NYSSILR B-50 Course ILR, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 57)
- Extension Division general, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 58)
- NYSSILR Extension Division General, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Extension Division - General, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- NYSSILR Extension Division Institutes and Courses, etc., 1953 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- NYSSILR Extension Division Memoranda, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Extension Division Reports - Quarterly 300-1, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Extension Division - Correspondence Albany Extension Division (Capital District Office), 1958 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Extension Division - Correspondence Buffalo Extension Division (Western District Office), 1957 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- NYSSILR Extension Division Correspondence, Albany, New York City, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- NYSSILR Extension Division Correspondence Ithaca, New York, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- NYSSILR Extension Division Correspondence - New York Office, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Extension Division - Correspondence New York Extension Division (Metropolitan District Office), 1958 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- NYSSILR Extension Division Correspondence, Buffalo, New York, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Extension Division - Correspondence Ithaca Extension Division (Headquarters), 1958 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- NYSSILR Extension Division Records - State Library Requests, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- NYSSILR Extension Division Reports, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Research - Research and Information Division, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Extension Division Records - State Library Requests, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Office of Resident Instruction Graduate Assistants, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Memorandums, 1959-1970 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- B. NYSSILR B-65 ILR Student Organizations (Box 5, Folder 20)
- NYSSILR Industrial Relations Research Association, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Office of Resident Instruction Memoranda - Graduate and Undergraduate Students, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Office of Resident Instruction Course -- J. G. Miller, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Office of Resident Instruction Placement Program, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Office of Resident Instruction Advisory System - Undergraduates, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Office of Resident Instruction Advisory System - Graduates, 1957-1964 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- NYSSILR Course Material ILR 590 - 1957-58, 1957-1958 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Library, NYSSILR Procedures General, 1947-1965 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Library, NYSSILR Procedures 1948-49, 1948-1949 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Library, NYSSILR Procedures 1948-49, 1948-1949 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Library, NYSSILR Section Reports Catalog, 1949-1950 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Library, NYSSILR Section Reports, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Library, NYSSILR Regulations (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Library, NYSSILR Memoranda to Administrative Ass't. Extra Copies, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Library, NYSSILR Annual Reports (Mrs. Snyder- Estimated earnings) 1960- (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Library - Reports Special Service Analysis-Division of the Budget, N.Y.S. Ed. Dept. (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Cornell University Library - Monthly Reports, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Cornell University Library - Monthly Reports, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Library Reports - Special Reports-Monthly Reports CU Library, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Library, NYSSILR Special Reports - Monthly Statistically Report (CUL), 1956-1958 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Library, NYSSILR Special Reports - Monthly Statistical Report, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Library, NYSSILR Special Reports - Monthly Statistical Report (CUL), 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Library, NYSSILR Special Reports, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Library, NYSSILR Special Reports, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Library, NYSSILR Special Reports, 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Library, NYSSILR, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Library, NYSSILR Special Reports - Monthly Statistical (CUL), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Library, NYSSILR Special Reports - Monthly Statistics (CUL), 1963 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Library, NYSSILR Special Reports (Monthly Report), 1963 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Cornell University Library - Acquisitions Section Reports, 1952-1953 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Library, NYSSILR Unit Reports Acquisitions, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Library, NYSSILR Unit Reports Acquisitions, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Library, NYSSILR Unit Reports Acquisitions, 1959-1960 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Library, NYSSILR Acquisitions Dept., 1960 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Library, NYSSILR Acquisitions Dept., 1963 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Library, NYSSILR Unit Reports Audio Visual, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Library, NYSSILR Unit Reports Audio-Visual, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Library, NYSSILR Unit Reports Audio-Visual, 1959-1960 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Library, NYSSILR Audio-Visual Unit, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Library, NYSSILR Audio-Visual Unit July, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Library, NYSSILR Section Reports Catalog Unit - Current, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Library, NYSSILR Unit Reports Catalog Unit, 1958-1959 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Library, NYSSILR Unit Reports Catalog Unit, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Library, NYSSILR Unit Reports Catalog Unit, 1959-1960 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Library, NYSSILR Catalog Unit, 1960-1962 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Library, NYSSILR Catalog Unit, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Library, NYSSILR Section Reports Circulation and References, 1950-1951 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Library, NYSSILR Section Reports Circulation and Reference Current, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Library, NYSSILR Section Reports Circulation, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Library, NYSSILR Unit Reports Circulation Unit, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Library, NYSSILR Unit Reports Circulation Unit, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Library, NYSSILR Unit Reports Circulation Unit, 1959-1960 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Library, NYSSILR Circulation Unit, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Library, NYSSILR Circulation Unit, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Library, NYSSILR Reports - Reference Unit, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Library, NYSSILR Section Reports Labor-Management Documentation Center, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Library, NYSSILR Unit Reports Labor-Management Documentation Center, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Library, NYSSILR Unit Reports Labor-Management Documentation Center, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Library, NYSSILR Unit Reports Labor-Management Documentation Center, 1959-1960 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Library, NYSSILR Labor-Management Documentation Center, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Library, NYSSILR Labor-Management Documentation Center, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Library, NYSSILR Unit Reports Librarians' Office, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Library, NYSSILR Unit Reports Myron Taylor, 1957-1958 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Library, NYSSILR Unit Reports Myron Taylor, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Library, NYSSILR Unit Reports Myron Taylor, 1959-1960 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Library, NYSSILR Periodicals Unit (MT), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Library, NYSSILR Periodicals Unit, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Library, NYSSILR Furniture and Equipment, 1947-1948 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Library, NYSSILR Furniture and Equipment, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Library, NYSSILR Furniture and Equipment, 1955-1969 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Library, NYSSILR Supplies, General, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Library, NYSSILR Supplies, Catalog Unit, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Library, NYSSILR Supplies, Circulation Unit, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Library, NYSSILR Supplies, Librarian's Office, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Library, NYSSILR Supplies, Periodicals Unit - (Sakr), 1955 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Library, NYSSILR Intra School Memoranda, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Library, NYSSILR Printing, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Library, NYSSILR Printing - 1961 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Library, NYSSILR Repairs and General Maintenance, 1956-1969 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Library, NYSSILR Repairs and General Maintenance, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Library, NYSSILR Inter Library Memoranda Collection of Regional History, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Library, NYSSILR Inter Library Memoranda Cornell University Library Foreign Periodical Subscription, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Library, NYSSILR Intra University Memoranda Business Office (for State College), 1952 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Library, NYSSILR Finance, 1951-1953 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Library, NYSSILR Finance - Monthly Statements on Account, 1953-1955 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Library, NYSSILR Finance - Monthly Statements on Account, 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Budget Discussion, 1956-57, 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Library, NYSSILR Budget Discussion, 1957/58, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Finance - Budget Discussion, 1958/59, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Finance - Budget Discussion, 1959/60, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Finance - Budget Discussion, 1960/61, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Finance - Budget Discussion 1961/62, 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Finance - Comparison of ILR Budgets Alternative Years, 1953-1962 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Finance - Budget Discussion, 1963/64, 1963-1964 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Finance - Budget 1964/65, 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Finance - Budget 1965/66, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Finance - Budget 1966/67, 1966-1967 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Finance - Budget 1968/69, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Library, NYSSILR C-16 Publicity, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Finance - Budget 1967/68, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Budget - Long Range Planning, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Budget - Long Term Planning, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Finance - Budget Discussion, 1962/63, 1962-1963 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Library, NYSSILR Finance Memoranda, Doris Stevenson, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Memoranda - Doris Stevenson, 1954-1960 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Memoranda - Doris Stevenson, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Monthly Statements on Accounts, 1958-60, 1958-1960 (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Monthly Statements on Accounts 1960/61, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Monthly Statement of Transactions, 1965-1968 (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Monthly Statement of Transactions - 1967-68, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Library, NYSSILR Finance Budget, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 2)